==========================================================

Legally speaking, about your privacy using ESET.

**Privacy Policy**
==================

### **Table of contents:**

**PRIVACY POLICY**
==================

EFFECTIVE DATE: DECEMBER 6, 2022

This privacy policy (“**Policy**”) describes how ESET North America and its affiliates and subsidiaries (“**ESET**,” “**we**” or “**us**”) collect, use, disclose, and otherwise process the personal information described in this Policy. This Policy applies to the extent we process personal information as a business or controller.

Your use of [eset.com/us/](https://www.eset.com/us/) (the “**Site**”) and the services and products we provide (“**Services**”) is subject to this Policy and our [Terms of Use](https://www.eset.com/us/policy-hub/legal-information/) or [End User License Agreement](https://help.eset.com/eula/?lang=en). By using the Site, you expressly accept and consent that your information may be transferred across international borders to server locations supporting the Site (including but not limited to transfers from those locations back to the country of your registration) for operating and developing the Site. This includes transfers to ESET subcontractors, agents, or representatives who perform tasks related to the Site and services, and transfers for the purpose of storing the data in relevant databases.

If you are a resident of California, please also refer to the tab “[Your California Rights](https://www.eset.com/us/policy-hub/your-california-rights/)” in this Policy Hub for further information about your rights under California privacy laws.

* * *

**1\. Scope**
-------------

This Policy applies to Personal Information we collect when you when you download and use ESET’s products or services, communicate with us, or otherwise interact or engage with us or the services available through our website (collectively, the “Services”).

Our information practices depend on how you interact with our Services and which parts of our Site you visit. For example, the pages on our Site related to our business and enterprise solutions are intended for use by our business-to-business (“**B2B**”) customers, while pages related to our home solutions are intended for use by individual customers. ESET distributors and resellers (“**Partners**”) have access to the ESET Partner Portal, which contains educational programs and other resources. The information we collect from B2B customers, individual customers, and Partners may vary as described below.

This Policy does not apply to the information that we collect and process about ESET employees or job applicants. If you are an employee or applicant of ESET, please refer to the ESET Employee Privacy Policy and ESET Applicant Privacy Policy for more information. If you are an independent contractor of ESET who resides in California, you may exercise your rights as described in the “California Privacy Rights” tab above. 

* * *

**2\. Personal Information We Collect and How We Use It**
---------------------------------------------------------

We collect information that identifies, describes, or can reasonably be associated with you (“**Personal Information**”). Personal Information does not include publicly available information in government records or any data that has been deidentified, aggregated, or otherwise anonymized.

### **Visiting Our Site**

The personal information we have collected directly from you may include:

* **Identifiers.** We collect your IP address, device ID, and other online identifiers;
* **Internet or Network Activity Information.** We collect your browsing history and interactions with our website, including domain name, page views, a date/time stamp, browser type, device type, internet service provider, referring and exiting URLs, operating system, language, clickstream data, and similar device and usage information;
* **Geolocation Information.** We may be able to infer your general location based on your IP address; and
* **Audio, Electronic, and Similar Information.** We collect records of messages you send via our customer service web chat feature.

We use this information to help us run our site securely and enable basic functions like page loading or navigation. Some cookies we use help us analyze how you interact with our site, including which items you may view or consider. This data enables us to improve our site’s look, feel, and performance, and identify our best-selling trends. Cookies also allow us to deliver advertisements that are meaningful to you. For more information, see the Cookie Policy tab above.

### **Contacting Customer Service**

If you contact customer service for questions, comments, or feedback, we collect the following Personal Information:

* **Identifiers**. This includes your name and contact information, which may be your email address and/or phone number depending on whether you contact us online or over the phone;
* **Commercial Information**. This includes your order history if you made a purchase;
* **Audio, Electronic, and Similar Information**. We collect voice and video recordings if you call us or send us video content;
* **Employment Information**. If you are a B2B customer, we may collect the name of your employer and your job title; and
* **Other Information You Provide**. We collect your comments and other details about your request for customer support.

We use this information to respond to your request for customer support. We take your comments and feedback seriously, so we may also learn from this information to improve our quality assurance and for training purposes.

### **Making a Purchase**

If you purchase any of our Services on the Site, we collect the following Personal Information to process your payments and fulfill your orders:

* **Personal Identifiers**. This includes your name, phone number, email address, and mailing address;
* **Commercial Information**. This includes transaction information and your order history;
* **Financial Information**. This includes your payment method and billing address; and
* **Company Information**. If you are a B2B customer, we may collect the name of your company, job title and contact information.

### **Signing Up for an ESET Partner Account**

If you create a Partner account, we collect the following Personal Information to establish your account:

* **Personal Identifiers**. Including your Company name, name, phone number, email address, and mailing address;
* **Account Information**. This includes your username, and account preferences;
* **Commercial Information**. This includes your order history or any items you may have marked as a favorite and saved; and
* **Financial Information**. This includes your payment method and billing address.

### **Joining our Mailing List**

If you join our Partner mailing list, we collect your email address from you to provide you with information about products, events, or promotional opportunities that may interest you. You can unsubscribe by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any ESET email.

### **Interacting with Us on Social Media**

If you follow or friend us on any social networking platforms, such as Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn, and Instagram, both ESET and/or the social media platform may collect Personal Information about you, including:

* **Personal Identifiers.** This includes the username of handle you use for that social media platform;
* **Content You Post.** We may collect content you share or post on ESET’s pages or threads; and
* **Social Media Contacts.** Depending on your privacy settings, we may collect your contacts, followers, or friends on that social media platform.

We use the information we receive through social media to enhance our social media presence, improve our products, and deliver relevant information about promotional opportunities, marketing materials, or other incentives. We do not control and are not responsible for how social media platforms use the information they may collect about you when you use social media. Instead, you should look to the social media platform’s privacy policy and terms to understand their practices or control your choices.

### **Registering for Live Events and Webinars**

If you sign up for our live events or webinars, we may collect Personal Information about you, including:

* **Personal Identifiers**. Including your name, phone number, email address, and mailing address;
* **Audio, Electronic, and Similar Information**. We may record our live events, so we may collect your voice and/or video recordings if you participate, such as by asking a question; and
* **Employment Information**. We may collect the name of your employer and your job title.

We use this information for event planning and management, including registration, attendance, connecting you with other event attendees, and contacting you about relevant events and Services.

* * *

**3\. How We Share Personal Information**
-----------------------------------------

We disclose the personal information we collect for the purposes described below:

* **Services and Support**. To provide and operate our Services, communicate with you about your use of the Services, provide troubleshooting and technical support, respond to your inquiries, fulfill your orders and requests, process your payments, communicate with you, and for similar service and support purposes.
* **Analytics and Improvement**. To better understand how you access and use the Services, and our other products and offerings, and for other research and analytical purposes, such as to evaluate and improve our services and business operations, to develop services and features, and for internal quality control and training purposes.
* **Marketing, Advertising, and Campaign Management**. We may disclose certain information that includes personal information to third-party ad network providers and/or traffic measurement services, which may use this data to improve and measure the effectiveness of our ads. For more information, see the Cookie Policy tab above.
* **In Support of Business Transfers**. If we or our affiliates are or may be acquired by, merged with, or invested in by another company, or as part of a financing, or if any of our assets are or may be transferred to another company, whether as part of a bankruptcy or insolvency proceeding or otherwise, we may transfer the information we have collected from you to the other company.  We may also share certain personal information as necessary prior to the completion of such a transfer, such as to lenders, auditors, and third-party advisors, including attorneys and consultants, as part of due diligence or as necessary to plan for the transfer.
* **Compliance, Governance, and Legal Requirements**. To comply with legal obligations, to respond to legal process and related legal proceedings. For example, we may disclose information in response to subpoenas, court order, and other lawful requests by regulators and law enforcement, including responding to national security or law enforcement disclosure requirements.  We may also disclose information, including personal information, related to litigation and other legal claims or proceedings in which we are involved, as well as for our internal accounting, auditing, compliance, recordkeeping, and legal functions. In addition, we may disclose the names of sweepstakes and contests winners, in accordance with applicable law.  
* **Security and Protection of Rights**. To protect the Services and our business operations; to prevent and detect fraud, unauthorized activities and access, and other misuse; to protect our rights, those of stakeholders and any third party; where we believe necessary to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety or legal rights of any person or third party, or violations of our  Terms of Use or End User License Agreement or this Policy.

We may disclose and make available personal information, for the purposes described above, to the following parties:

* **Vendors and Service Providers**. We may disclose personal information we collect to our service providers, processors, agents, and others who perform functions on our behalf. These vendors may include, for example, analytics providers, marketing firms, consultants, payment processors, auditors, and legal counsel.
* **Our Subsidiaries and Affiliates**. We may disclose personal information we collect to our subsidiaries and affiliates.
* **Third-Party Ad Networks**. We may disclose personal information to third-party ad networks, sponsors, and/or traffic measurement services. These third parties may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (including clear GIFs), and other tracking technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content to you. These third-party cookies and other technologies are governed by each third party's specific privacy policy, not this one. To exercise your choices about receiving third-party ads, see the Cookie Policy tab above.
* **Others as Permitted by Applicable Law**. We may also disclose personal information to third parties to the extent required by applicable law and legal or contractual obligations. This may include regulators, government entities, law enforcement as required by law or legal process, as well as potential and actual acquirors, business partners or financiers and their employees, representatives, and counsel. We may also disclose personal information to lenders, auditors, and third-party advisors, including attorneys and consultants.

* * *

**4\. Children's Privacy**
--------------------------

Our Services are not designed for children, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information in violation of applicable law, we will delete such information from our systems. If you are a parent and you believe we have collected your child’s information in violation of applicable law, please contact us as set forth in the section below titled “Contact Us.”

* * *

**5\. Retention**
-----------------

We retain your Personal Information for as long as needed, or permitted, based on the reason why we obtained it (consistent with applicable law). When deciding how long to keep your information, we consider whether we are subject to any legal obligations (e.g., any laws that require us to keep records for a certain period of time before we can delete them) or whether we have taken any legal positions (e.g., issued any legal holds or otherwise need to preserve the information). From time to time, we may also deidentify your Personal Information, retain it and use it for a business purpose in compliance with CCPA. .

* * *

**6\. External Links and Features**
-----------------------------------

Our Services may contain links to third-party websites or features. Any access to and use of such linked websites or features is not governed by this Policy, but instead is governed by the privacy policies of those third parties. We are not responsible for the information practices of such third parties, including their collection of your Personal Information. You should review the privacy policies and terms for any third parties before proceeding to those websites or using those features.

* * *

**7\. Changes to this Policy**
------------------------------

This Policy is current as of the Effective Date set forth above. We may change this Policy from time to time, so please be sure to check back periodically. We will post any updates to Policy here.

* * *

**8\. Contact Us**
------------------

If you have any comments or questions regarding ESET's Privacy Policy, please contact our Privacy Officer by telephone at: (619) 876-5576; by email at: [privacy@eset.com](javascript:linkTo_UnCryptMailto(%27ftbemh3ikbotvrTxlxm7vhf%27);); or by mail at:

Privacy Officer  
ESET North America  
655 W Broadway, Suite 700  
San Diego, CA 92101

    [Home Security](https://www.eset.com/us/home/protection-plans/) Home Security

    ### [HOME Security](https://www.eset.com/us/brand-special-offer/) 50% OFF
    
    [All-in-one protection of your digital life. Choose a plan according to your needs.](https://www.eset.com/int/home/protection-plans/)

    **Special solutions:**

    [All-in-one protection](https://www.eset.com/us/home/protection-plans/) All-in-one protection
    
    HOME Security
    
    All-in-one protection of your digital life. Choose a plan according to your needs.

    Special offers for:

    [Device protection](https://www.eset.com/us/home/protection-plans/) Device protection

    #### [**ESET NOD32  
    Antivirus**](https://www.eset.com/us/home/antivirus/)
    
    Award-winning antivirus for Windows and macOS

    #### **[ESET Mobile Security for Android](https://www.eset.com/us/home/mobile-security-android/)  
    **
    
    Keep your Android device safe. Wherever you go

    #### [**ESET Parental Control for Android**](https://www.eset.com/us/home/parental-control-android/)
    
    Protect your children online with confidence
    
    [Small Office](https://www.eset.com/us/for-home/small-business-security/) Small Office

    ### [Small office security](https://www.eset.com/int/home/small-business-security/) 25% OFF
    
    [Reliable and user-friendly protection tailor made for small offices.](https://www.eset.com/int/home/small-business-security/)

    **Complete security for small offices:**
    
    * Malware, ransomware and phishing protection​
    * Non stop Safe Banking ​
    * Encryption of sensitive data​
    * Unlimited VPN

    [WHY ESET](https://www.eset.com/us/home/why-eset/) WHY ESET

    ### **ENJOY WHAT MATTERS,** **  
    LEAVE THE REST TO ESET**
    
    Learn what makes our acclaimed online security solution special and how it can help you protect your devices. 

    [Renew & Support](https://www.eset.com/us/existing-customers/) Renew & Support
    
    Explore the ESET Customer Portal to:
    
    * Renew, add devices or upgrade your product
    * Retrieve your subscription information
    * Update your subscription and billing information
    * Find help with product installation
    * Get additional technical support

    [Business Solutions](https://www.eset.com/us/business/small-and-medium/) Business Solutions

    #### **[BUSINESS  
    SOLUTIONS](https://www.eset.com/us/business/small-and-medium/)**
    
    Protect your company endpoints,  
    business data and users

    #### Recommended solutions
    
    * [ESET PROTECT Complete](https://www.eset.com/us/business/cyber-week-2024/) 25% OFF
    * [ESET PROTECT Advanced](https://www.eset.com/us/business/cyber-week-2024/) 25% OFF
    
    #### Recommended services

    [Enterprise Solutions](https://www.eset.com/us/business/enterprise/) Enterprise Solutions

    #### **[ENTERPRISE  
    SOLUTIONS](https://www.eset.com/us/business/enterprise/)**
    
    Future-ready cybersecurity  
    for powerful enterprise protection

    #### Recommended solutions
    
        All-in-one protection with premium 24/7 MDR service
    * [**ESET PROTECT Elite**](https://www.eset.com/us/business/cyber-week-2024/) 25% OFF  
        All-in-one protection with XDR to prevent breaches
    
    #### Recommended services

    #### Tailored solutions

    [ESET Services](https://www.eset.com/us/business/services/) ESET Services

    #### **[ESET SERVICES](https://www.eset.com/us/business/services/)**
    
    Choose from the Extensive Range of  
    ESET Services

    #### Recommended services

    [ESET Platform](https://www.eset.com/us/business/protect-platform/) ESET Platform

    #### **[ESET PROTECT PLATFORM](https://www.eset.com/us/business/protect-platform/)**
    
    Learn more about our unified cybersecurity platform and its uniquely balanced capabilities.

    Platform modules

    [Partner with ESET](https://www.eset.com/us/business/partner/msp/) Partner with ESET

    #### **[BECOME AN ESET PARTNER](https://www.eset.com/us/partnernow/)**
    
    Explore ESET partnerships designed to boost your growth.

    #### Already an ESET Partner?  
    **Welcome back!**
    
    Log in now to place orders, register opportunities, access training and much more!

    [Contact Sales](https://www.eset.com/us/about/contact/) Contact Sales
    
    #### **For business sales call:**

    MONDAY - FRIDAY, 6AM - 5PM PT
    
    #### More contact options

    [Why ESET](https://www.eset.com/us/business/why-eset/industry-analysts-recognition/) Why ESET

    #### **[Why choose ESET?](https://www.eset.com/us/business/why-eset/)**
    
    ESET is built on trust and stability, allowing it to offer leading technology through research excellence.

    #### Additional information and resources

    #### Industries

    [Download](https://www.eset.com/us/download-c/version-c/) Download

    ### Download for  
    **Home and Small office**

    ### Download for  
    **Business**

    [Get a free home trial](https://www.eset.com/us/home/free-trial/) Get a free home trial
    
    [I have a home license](https://www.eset.com/us/download/home/) I have a home license
    
    [Get a free business trial](https://www.eset.com/us/business/trial/) Get a free business trial
    
    [I have a business license](https://www.eset.com/us/business/download/) I have a business license

**ESET North America**  
San Diego, California  

#### For home

#### Downloads for home

#### For business

#### Downloads for business

#### Partnership

#### Support

#### About ESET

#### Downloads for home

#### Downloads for business

**ESET North America**  
San Diego, California  

* * *

##### © 2008-2024 ESET North America. All rights reserved. Trademarks used herein are trademarks or registered trademarks of ESET spol. s r.o. or ESET North America. All other names and brands are registered trademarks of their respective companies.

5.32.0.mas.99fba1d3.awus
